Godfrey Ekalumele

IT And Communication Expert

Contact

Address
Abuja FCT 901007

Phone 07059586956

E-mail

Ekalumelegodfrey @gmail.com

Lindedin

www.lindedin.com/ ekalumele-godfrey

Skills

Frontend Developer

Adobe Suite

Graphics Design

Computer Repair

Microsoft Office

Result-oriented IT and Communication Expert Successfull at applying technical skills and training to create arts that informs and engages customers. Clear communicator and collaborative team player with an eye for detail and in customer relations.

Work History

2021-05 -2023-03

Operations Manager, IT and Communication Expert

Peniel Gerar Int'l Limited, Kano, Kano State.

- Devised Processes to boost long-term business success and increase profit levels.
- Established positive and effective communication among unit staff and organisation leadership, reducing miscommunications, and missed deadlines.
- Introduced new ethods, practices, and systems to reduce turnaround time.
- Implemented process improveent to shape organizational culture, optimize procedures for higher efficiency and help company evolve and grow.
- Designed a microsoft excel program to determine profit margin. This program aided in analysing total cost price and recommending selling price, thereby minimizing production cost, by putting the selling price in focus.

2020 - 04 -2021- 06

Graphics Designer/Social Media Manager

E.O.E Jason Global Nigeria Limited, Abuja, FCT.

- Created graphics design and photo content for social media handles.
- Organized social media advertisement campaign on facebook, Instagram and youtube platforms to targeted market in preferred locations.
- Completed final touches for projects such as images, sizes and font selection.
- Develop Creative designs for print materials, brochoures, banners and signs.
- Created digital image fliers for use in digital and traditional printing methods.

Recent Training

Tiidelab Prefellowship 3.0

- Abuja, FCT.
- ~completed, 2023

ALX Software Enginering

- Remote
- ~running

Interests

-Learning -problem-solving -Teaching 2016 -10 -2020 - 01

Technical Instructor

Elite Private Lessons, Ekpoma, Edo State.

- Compiled IT training and assessent resources based on understanding of technical processes and skill-development needs.
- Oversaw technical documentation, instruction and evaluation to meet IT education initiative.
- Created courseware using online learning management system tool and various graphics and multimedia software programs.

2015 -06 -2015 - 11

IPPIS Machine Operator (Intenship)

NIFOR Computer Department, Benin City, Edo State.

- Demonstrated respect, friendless and willingness to support where needed.
- Applied effective time management techniques to meet tight deadlines.
- Completed paperwork, recognizing discrepancies and promptly addressing for resolutions.
- Repaired over 15 HP desktop computers, Installed operating system software and troubleshooting of office printers.

Education

2014 - 10 -2018 - 11 **Bsc: Computer Science**

Ambrose Alli University - Ekpoma, Edo State.

Accomplishments

- Used Microsoft Excel to develop inventory tracking spreadsheets.
- O Achieved remote meeting efficiency by introducing recommended softwares and technology for real time meeting simulation and document sharing.
- O Achieved results by conducting market analysis that resulted in deterining selling price and market projections with accuracy and efficiency.

Supervised team of 8 staff members and over 20-30 daily workers.